Ladies and
gentlemen,
I always
see comments
under
my videos
like,
"How
do you
invest
your money?"
But
that's
not really
a good
question,
and here's
why at
this
point
I'm investing
millions
and millions
of dollars.
But 90%
of you
aren't
there
yet,
so what
I do
is not
going
to apply
to you.
But since
you
guys
are curious
and I
find
this
to be
a rather
interesting
topic,
I decided
that
today
I'm going
to share
how I
would
invest
a thousand
dollars
if I
wasn't
a multi-millionaire.
And I want
to promise
you one
thing,
now by
the end
of this
video
you will
know
how to
turn
a thousand
into
ten
thousand
or
even
a hundred
thousand
dollars
in
days
or less.
And yes,
I'm
aware
that that's
a massive
claim,
but I
don't
expect
you to take
my word
for it.